Alexander Ulogov

Full Stack Web Developer

I am a full stack web developer with more than fifteen years of hands-on experience. I have a strong background in web development and have worked on a wide range of projects from simple websites to complex web applications.

I am a self-motivated, hard-working, and goal-oriented person. I am able to work independently and as part of a team.

Experience

2003 – 2022 · Freelance · Numerous Clients *Full Stack Web Developer*

- Discuss clients' business needs and develop custom web solutions
- Develop and use my own framework
- Work with web designers
- Maintain and update websites
- Generate dynamic business and accounting reports
- Search engine optimization

2007 – 2017 · Online Plumbing Store Mirsanteh

Full Stack Web Developer

- Help to grow business from a small brick-and-mortar plumbing store to one of the top three Russian online plumbing stores
- Build a very complex online store from the ground up
- Build a module to exchange data with accounting software
- Create dynamically generated business reports
- Troubleshoot and resolve technical issues
- Work with SEO and advertising agencies

2003 – 2006 · Online Toy Store Neopod

Full Stack Web Developer

- Develop a website for a small family toy store
- Develop an accounting tool
- Toy market research
- Help to grow and sell the business

Education

1996 – 2001 Moscow, Russia State University of Management Bachelor's degree, Financial Management

Contact

Jacksonville, Florida, US

+1 (334) 552-22-29

alulogov@gmail.com

www.alexu.dev

www.linkedin.com/in/aulogov

Skills

Main stack:

PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks:

Laravel (PHP), Flask (Python), Bootstrap, jQuery

Other:

SEO, MVC, JSON, XML, Rest API, Git

Deployment:

Digital Ocean, Linode, Ubuntu, Nginx, Apache

Languages

English	
Russian	

Interests

- Playing Soccer
- Woodworking
- Playing Chess